<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Armand Carstens</title>
    <link>https://armand-carstens.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Armand Carstens</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 15:44:22 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://armand-carstens.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to Code (Part 3)</title>
      <link>https://armand-carstens.github.io/howtocode/part3htc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 15:44:22 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://armand-carstens.github.io/howtocode/part3htc/</guid>
      <description>Defining Basics (Part 2) Conditionals In programming we have conditional terms to the fact that:
Most/ I mean ALL of programming is conditional Every single programming language &amp;hellip; Understanding the logic gate ideological connection behind coding Such as programming microcontrollers Arduino&amp;rsquo;s C library, Raspberry Pi&amp;rsquo;s own IDE in a custom OS etc. Thus leading to the discrete mathematical inductions of computers Understanding math behind it such as De Morgan&amp;rsquo;s law for Date-Range calculation etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Code (Part 2)</title>
      <link>https://armand-carstens.github.io/howtocode/part2htc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 08:44:07 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://armand-carstens.github.io/howtocode/part2htc/</guid>
      <description>Defining Basics Since you&amp;rsquo;ve chosen a starting point, I&amp;rsquo;d state the easiest one I know myself. The main goal of the series is to guide you all the way to linked lists and OOP.
My parameters are as follows Python as a compiler and source code. My own current knowledge of the language. Explaining Turing technology with a simple example. Casting So, the first thing everyone should know is that the equal sign operator is a CAST.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Code (Part 1)</title>
      <link>https://armand-carstens.github.io/howtocode/part1htc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 12:13:10 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://armand-carstens.github.io/howtocode/part1htc/</guid>
      <description>Background To start coding, one should have &amp;lsquo;ikigai&amp;rsquo; to maintain a happy relationship with your new hobby/career. Instead of finding yourself too broke to live your passion or in a scenario where you suck at something, try and focus on maintaining the good in all areas.
This is &amp;lsquo;Ikigai&amp;rsquo; visually: How to start ? The key to any skill if it be rugby players or mathematicians is to have a good foundational comprehension.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <link>https://armand-carstens.github.io/blog/introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 16:44:15 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://armand-carstens.github.io/blog/introduction/</guid>
      <description>Hello World, I am Armand 😊 As some of you may know, I have an obsession when it comes to PC and AI development. I am currently dedicating this blog to sharing my findings as a Junior Developer.
Corporate Life To introduce myself, I work for a consultancy firm that develops software for Project Management in SAP systems for both international and national level companies. My job includes the following:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
